Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Deans Papers, 1929-1999, undated, 95 Linear Feet (63.5 boxes)
  - Dean H.Claude Horack,1933-1948, undated
    - Scholarship Announcements, 1932-1943, undated (Box 12)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1934-1935, undated (Box 12)
    - Secretarial Postings, 1933-1945, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Selective Service, 1940-1942, undated (Box 13)
    - enior Breakfast, 1935-1942, undated (Box 13)
    - September Graduation, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Shafroth, Will, 1935-1945, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Shepherd, Harold, 1939-1946, undated (Box 13)
    - The Sheppard Bill, 1939 (Box 13)
    - Smith, Willis, 1934-1946 (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - South Carolina Convention Cruise, 1936, undated (Box 13)
    - Spears, Marshall T., 1936 (Box 13)
    - Speeches, 1935-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Stanley, W.E., 1940-1942 (Box 13)
    - Stansbury, Dale F., 1938-1946, undated (Box 13)
    - Statistics, 1930-1941, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Stephenson, Gilbert T., 1937-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Stoddard, George, 1938 (Box 13)
    - Strong, Frank R., 1940, undated (Box 13)
    - The Student Movement in Bar Association Work by McGuire and Horack, undated (Box 13)
    - Student Selection Committee, 1939-1942, undated (Box 13)
    - Summer Law School Session Announcements, 1935 (Box 13)
    - Supreme Court, 1937, undated (Box 13)
    - Survey of Schools Material, 1937, undated (Box 13)
    - T Correspondence, 1934-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Teachers, Prospective, 1932-1946, undated (folder 1 of 5) (Box 13)
    - Teachers, Prospective, 1932-1946, undated (folders 2-5 of 5) (Box 14)
    - Teacher Recommendation Requests, 1935-1939, undated (Box 14)
    - Tenth Judicial District Bar, 1937-1941 (Box 14)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority Employment Information, 1942 (Box 14)
    - Telegrams, 1936-1938, undated (Box 14)
    - Texas, University of, at Austin, 1939-1940, undated (Box 14)
    - Tillett, Charles W., 1938-1946, undated (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Toledo, University of, College of Law, 1941, undated (Box 14)
    - Travelers Insurance Company, 1940-1941, undated (Box 14)
    - Trends in Legal Education, Report, 1938-1939, undated (Box 14)
    - Tuition Fees at Approved Law Schools for 1935-1936, undated (Box 14)
    - Tulane University, 1937-1939, undated (Box 14)
    - U Correspondence, 1935-1946, undated (Box 14)
    - Uhler, Armin, 1935-1937 (Box 14)
    - Uniform State Laws, 1938-1943, undated (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - United States Constitution: Sesquicentennial Commission, 1936-1938, undated (Box 14)
    - Updegraff, Clarence, 1939, undated (Box 14)
    - V Correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 14)
    - V-12 Navy Program, 1943, undated (Box 14)
    - Vanderbilt, Arthur T., 1937-1938 (Box 14)
    - Van Hecke, M.T. (Maurice Taylor), 1936-1941, undated (Box 14)
    - Van Winkle, Kingsland, 1939, undated (Box 14)
    - Vanity Fair Cartoons, 1934-1935 (Box 14)
    - Veterans' Administration, 1943-1947, undated (Box 14)
    - W Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Walker, Augusta, 1935-1936, undated (Box 15)
    - Wartime Program Announcement, 1942, undated (Box 15)
    - West Publishing Company, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Wettach, Robert H., 1941-1947 (Box 15)
    - Whitford, W.E., 1935-1945, undated (Box 15)
    - Witham, Henry B., 1937-1938 (Box 15)
    - Womble, B.S., 1934-1940 (Box 15)
    - Wright, De Witt, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
    - X, Y, Z Correspondence, 1936-1943, undated (Box 15)
  - Dean Harold Shepard, 1940-1949, undated
    Harold Shepard was dean of the law school from 1947-1949.
    - A Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 15)
    - Alumni Banquet, 1948, undated (Box 15)
    - American Bar Association, Section on Legal Education and Admissions to the Bar, 1946-1949, undated (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - American Bar Assocation, Survey of the Legal Profession, 1947-1949, undated (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - American Law Institute, 1946-1948 (Box 15)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1940-1949, undated (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - B Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 15)
    - Board of Trustees, 1947-1949 (Box 15)
    - C Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 15)
    - Case Studies, 1948-1949, undated (Box 15)
    - Class Census Enrollment Cards, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Class Census Enrollment Cards, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Committee on Selected Readings on Contracts, 1947 (Box 16)
    - Correctional School, 1947 (Box 16)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1940-1949, undated (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - D Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 16)
    - Dean's Annual Report, 1947 (Box 16)
    - Delta Theta Phi, 1947-1948, undated (Box 16)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1947-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - E Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 16)
    - Edens, President A. Hollis, 1948-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - Enrollment Rosters and Figures, 1947 (Box 16)
    - F Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - Faculty Personnel Applications, 1945-1949, undated (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Flowers, Dr. R.L., 1946-1948 (Box 16)
    - G Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 16)
    - Graduate Study Committee, 1947-1948, undated (Box 16)
    - H Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 16)
    - Institute of Government, Legislative Service, Daily Legislative Bulletin, 1949 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Inter-American Bar Association, Report by H.C. Horack, 1948-1949 (Box 16)
    - J Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 16)
    - James F. Byrnes Senate Prize, 1947-1949 (Box 16)
    - Journal of Legal Education, 1948-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - K Correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 16)
    - Kappa Beta Pi, Legal Sorority, 1947-1948 (Box 16)
    - L Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1947-1950 (Box 16)
    - Law School Miscellaneous, 1947, undated (Box 16)
    - Law School Admission Test, 1947-1949, undated (Box 16)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 1947-1949 (Box 16)
    - Loan Funds, 1948 (Box 16)
    - Loyalty Fund, 1948, undated (Box 16)
    - M Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - M Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Markham, C.B., 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - Memoranda to Faculty, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1947-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - Misc. Correspondence Handled by Prof. Shepherd Summer, 1946 (Box 17)
    - N correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - New Plan, 1941-1946, undated (Box 17)
    - N.C. Bar Association, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - N.C. Commission for the Improvement of the Administration of Justice, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - NC. Court Records, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - N.C. State Bar, 1947-1948 (Box 17)
    - O Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - Order of the Coif, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - P Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Personnel Department, 1948-1951, undated (Box 17)
    - Phi Alpha Delta Fraternity Correspondence, 1938-1948 (Box 17)
    - Positions Available, 1947-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - R Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Retirement Policy of the University, undated (Box 17)
    - Rules of the Law School, 1947 (Box 17)
    - S Correspondence, 1946-1949, undated (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - Schedules, Exams and Classes, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Secretarial Positions, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - Shingle Jingle, undated (Box 17)
    - Southeastern Regional Conference of Law Teachers, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - Southern Law Review Conference, 1947-1948 (Box 17)
    - Staff, memos from, 1947, undated (Box 17)
    - Student Assistants, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - Sullivan and Cromwell, Francis Elwood Barkman, 1948 (Box 17)
    - Summer School, 1947-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - Symposium on Pre-Legal Education, 1948-1949, undatd (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - T Correspondence, 1948 (Box 17)
    - Telegrams and Long Distance Calls, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Undergraduate Activities - Misc., 1948-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - University Administrative committee (A.S. Brower), 1947-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - V Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Veterans Administration, 1945-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - W Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
    - Washington College of Law (Mr. Hubbard), 1946-1948, undated (Box 17)
    - West Publishing Company, 1946-1949 (Box 18)
    - Will Drafting Contest, 1949, undated (Box 18)
  - Dean Charles L. B. Lowndes (Acting Dean), 1949-1951, undated
    Charles Lowndes was acting dean of the law school from 1949 to 1950.
    - Correspondence, April - September 1949 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, October 1949 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, November 1949 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, December 1949 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, January 1950 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, February - March 1950 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, April 1950 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, May - August 1950, undated (Box 18)
    - Law Library, undated (Box 18)
    - Prolocuter, 1950, undated (Box 18)
    - Report to President Edens, 1950, undated (Box 18)
    - Student Payrolls, 1949-1951 (Box 18)
  - Dean Joseph McClain, Jr., 1933-1957, undated (bulk 1950-1956)
    Joseph McClain Jr. served as dean of the law school from 1950-1956. These files include several folders from his work before joining the Duke Law School; they relate to a California legal survey and are located at the end of this records subseries.
    - A Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 18)
    - Alumni Activities, 1951-1958, undated (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1951 (Box 18)
    - American Bar Association, 1950-1956 (Box 18)
    - American Bar Association, American Law Student Association, 1952-1957, undated (Box 18)
    - American Bar Association, Section on Legal Education and Admissions to the Bar, 1950-1954, undated (Box 18)
    - American Bar Assocation, Survey of the Legal Profession, 1950-1952, undated (Box 18)
    - American Bar Foundation, 1954-1956 (Box 18)
    - American Judicature Society, 1954-1956 (Box 18)
    - American Law Institute, 1951-1956 (Box 18)
    - Announcements, 1951-1952 (Box 18)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1950-1956, undated (1 of 3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1950-1956, undated (2 of 3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1950-1956, undated (2 of 3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Assocation of American Law Schools, Committee on Law School Administration and University Relations, 1955-1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Assocation of American Law Schools, Regarding: Yale Ammendment, 1950-1951, undated (Box 19)
    - B Correspondence, 1950-1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Bar Rag, undated (Box 19)
    - Bench and Bar Society (Box 19)
    - Board of Trustees, 1950 (Box 19)
    - Bradway, John S., 1950-1952 (Box 19)
    - Brochure (Proposed) for School of Law, 1938-1953, undated (Box 19)
    - Building Plans, 1950-1956 (Box 19)
    - C Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 19)
    - Case Studies, 1950-1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Class Census Reports, 1951-1956 (Box 19)
    - Commencement, 1951-1956 (Box 19)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1951-1952, undated (Box 19)
    - D Correspondence, 1950-1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Deanship, Resignation and Search for Successor, 1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Department of Justice Seminar, 1949-1951 (Box 19)
    - Duke Bar Association Constitution, 1953 (Box 19)
    - Duke Bar Journal, 1950-1957, undated (Box 19)
    - Duke Loyalty Fund, 1954-1955, undated (Box 19)
    - Dukes, Charles A., 1953-1957 (Box 19)
    - E Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 19)
    - Edens, A. Hollis, 1950-1956, undated (Box 19)
    - Educational Testing Service, 1952-1954, undated (Box 19)
    - Equity Rules, undated (Box 19)
    - F Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 19)
    - Faculty (Biographical Information), undated (Box 19)
    - Faculty Committees, 1950-1951 (Box 19)
    - Faculty Personnel Applications, 1946-1956, undated (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Foundation Press, 1953-1954 (Box 20)
    - Foundation Press, 1953-1954 (Box 20)
    - Frampton, George, T., 1953-1954 (Box 20)
    - G Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 20)
    - General Statutes Commission, 1954, undated (Box 20)
    - Gross, Paul, 1950-1951 (Box 20)
    - H Correspondence, 1950-1956 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - I Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 20)
    - Inauguration at University of North Carolina, 1950 (Box 20)
    - Institute of Judicial Administration, 1953-1955 (Box 20)
    - Insurance Law Center, 1951-1952, undated (Box 20)
    - Inter-American Bar Assocation, 1940-1955, undated (Box 20)
    - J Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 20)
    - James F. Byrnes Senate Prize, Delta Theta Phi Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 20)
    - Journal of Legal Education, 1950-1956, undated (Box 20)
    - K Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 20)
    - Kramer, Robert, 1950 (Box 20)
    - L Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 20)
    - Latty, E. R., 1952-1953, undated (Box 20)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1950-1956 (Box 20)
    - Law Library, 1950-1956 (2 Folders) (Box 20)
    - Law School Admissions Test, 1951-1952 (Box 20)
    - Law School Bulletin, 1950 (Box 20)
    - Law School Student Organizations, 1955-1956 (Box 20)
    - Lawyers Co-Operative Publishing company Awards, 1953-1956 (Box 20)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 1950-1956, undated (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - M Correspondence, 1950-1956, undated (Box 20)
    - Mc Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 20)
    - McClain, Joseph, (Dean), undated (Box 20)
    - McDermott, Malcolm (Portrait of), 1953-1954, undated (Box 20)
    - Markham, C.B., Memos To, 1951-1952 (Box 20)
    - Marshall, Chief Justice John (Portrait of), 1953-1957, undated (Box 20)
    - Marshall, John, Papers Regarding Portrait of, 1928-1940, undated (Box 20)
    - Michigan Recruitment by Donald G. Corley, 1956 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1954 (Box 20)
    - Moot Court Competition, 1950-1956 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - N Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 20)
    - Nathan Burkan Memorial Competition, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - Nathan Burkan Memorial Competition, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - National Conference of Bar Examiners, 1952-1953 (Box 21)
    - Newsletters to Alumni, 1950-1955, undated (Box 21)
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1954 (Box 21)
    - North Carolina Bar Assocation, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - North Carolina Board of Bar Examiners, 1947-1952, undated (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - North Carolina Board of Law Examiners, 1952-1956, undated (Box 21)
    - North Carolina College at Durham, 1955 (Box 21)
    - North Carolina General Court Records, 1952, undated (Box 21)
    - O Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 21)
    - Ohio Recruitment by John Carahan and Lyman Brownfield, 1955-1956 (Box 21)
    - Order of the coif, 1952-1955, undated (Box 21)
    - P Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - Paschal, J. Francis, 1953-1954, undated (Box 21)
    - Personnel Office, 1951-1956, undated (Box 21)
    - Petitions, 1954-1955, undated (Box 21)
    - Placement, 1951-1956 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Prizes, 1956-1957, undated (Box 21)
    - Prolocuter, 1952-1956 (Box 21)
    - Publications of Faculty, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - Q Correspondence, 1955 (Box 21)
    - R Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 21)
    - Regional Law Scholarships, 1954-1956, undated (Box 21)
    - Reorganization of General Faculty of Duke University, 1951-1952, undated (Box 21)
    - Report to the President, 1951-1956 (Box 21)
    - Research and Writing, undated (Box 21)
    - S Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 21)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1950-1951 (Box 21)
    - Sanya, Dharmasakti (Dhamasak) - Thailand, 1952, undated (Box 21)
    - Scholarships, 1950-1956, undated (Box 21)
    - Selective Service, 1951-1952, undated (Box 21)
    - Shimm, Melvin G., 1953 (Box 21)
    - Smith, Willis, Prize, 1950-1956, undated (Box 21)
    - Social Security, 1950, undated (Box 21)
    - Southwestern Legal Center, 1951 (Box 21)
    - Southwestern Regional Conference for Law Teachers, 1950-1951 (Box 21)
    - Speakers to the Student Body, 1952-1956 (Box 21)
    - Speeches, 1950 (Box 21)
    - Spy and Sadler Pictures, 1951-1952, undated (Box 22)
    - T Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 22)
    - Teaching Prospects, 1953-1954, undated (Box 22)
    - Theses on File in the Law Library, 1953-1954 (Box 22)
    - Traffic Commission, 1956 (Box 22)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1954-1956 (Box 22)
    - U Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 22)
    - Undergraduate Preparation for the Study of Law: A Symposium Addressed to College Students on the Subject of Pre-Legal Education, 1950-1951 (Box 22)
    - Undergraduate Student Counselling on Military Service, 1951 (Box 22)
    - University Council, 1956 (Box 22)
    - V Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 22)
    - Veterans' Administration, 1950 (Box 22)
    - Visits to Colleges by Law School Representatives, 1954-1955, undated (Box 22)
    - W Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 22)
    - West Publishing Company (Miscellaneous), 1950-1955 (Box 22)
    - Whitford, W.E., 1950-1954 (Box 22)
    - Will Drafting Contest, 1951-1956, undated (Box 22)
    - X, Y, Z, Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 22)
    - Young, William F., 1952 (Box 22)
    - California Survey Correspondence, 1947-1948, undated (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - California Survey Correspondence, 1933, January-July 1949 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - California Survey Correspondence, August-December 1949 (Box 22)
    - California Trip, 1947, undated (Box 22)
  - Dean Dale F. Stansbury (Acting Dean), 1956-1957.
    Dale Stansbury served as acting dean of the law school from 1956 to 1957.
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1956-1957 (Box 22)
  - Dean Elvin Jack Latty, 1940-1968, undated (bulk 1958-1966)
    Elvin Jack Latty was dean of the law school from 1957 to 1966.
    - Adelaide, University of, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Administrative, Dean's Reports, 1966-1968, undated (Box 22)
    - Admissions, 1962-1967, undated (Box 22)
    - Advisory Council of Judges, 1965 (Box 22)
    - African Legal Education, 1961-1962 (Box 22)
    - Allen Building, 1962-1968 (Box 22)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1961-1963, undated (folder 1 of 2) (Box 22)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1961-1963, undated (folder 2 of 2) (Box 23)
    - Alumni Affairs, Law, 1958-1965, undated (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Alumni, Class of 1935, 1963-1965, undated (Box 23)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1961-1967 (Box 23)
    - American Association of University Professors, Duke Chapter, 1959-1961, undated (Box 23)
    - American Bar Association, 1957-1965, undated (4 folders) (Box 23)
    - American Bar Association, American Law Student Association, 1958-1966, undated (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - American Bar Association, Committee on Continuing Legal Education, 1960-1961 (Box 23)
    - American Bar Association, Committee on relations with Lawyers of Other Nations, 1961-1962 (Box 23)
    - American Bar Association, Section on Legal Education and Admissions to the Bar, 1958-1959, undated (Box 23)
    - American Bar Foundation, 1957-1962 (Box 23)
    - American Council of Education, Higher Education and National Affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 23)
    - American Foreign Law Association, 1957-1963, undated (Box 23)
    - American Journal of Comparative Law, American Assocation for the Comparative Study of Law, 1959-1963 (Box 23)
    - American Judicure Society, 1957-1959 (Box 23)
    - American Law Institute, 1957-1963 (Box 23)
    - American Medical Association, 1958-1960 (Box 23)
    - American Society for Legal History, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
    - American Society of International Law, 1960-1963 (Box 23)
    - Annual Reports, 1963-1966 (Box 24)
    - Appointments, Promotions and Tenure, 1963 (Box 24)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1960-1966, undated (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Committee on Business Administration, 1958-1960 (Box 24)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Foreign Exchange, 1956-1962, undated (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - B Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 24)
    - Baade, Hans W., 1958-1966, undated (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Babcock Foundation, 1958-1961, undated (Box 24)
    - Babcock Foundation, World Rule of Law Center, 1961-1965 (Box 24)
    - Bar Examinations (Other States), 1959-1961, undated (Box 24)
    - The Bar Rag Editions for 1959-1961, 1959-1961, undated (Box 24)
    - Bernstein, Neil, 1960, 1963 (Box 24)
    - Bill Prosser Evaluation (and Similar Data), 1960, undated (Box 24)
    - Bloomenthal, Harold S., 1962-1963, undated (Box 24)
    - Board of Legal Examiners, 1958-1965, undated (4 folders) (Box 24)
    - Bowdoin Campaign, 1962, undated (Box 24)
    - Bolich, William Bryan, 1957-1966, undated (Box 24)
    - Bradway, John, 1957-1959, undated (Box 25)
    - Brandon, John Michael, 1960-1964 (Box 25)
    - Bryson, Edwin Constant, 1958-1966 (Box 25)
    - Budget, 1961-1966 (Box 25)
    - Building Plans, 1962-1966, undated (Box 25)
    - Bulletin, Law School, 1958-1961 (Box 25)
    - Business Corporation Act (Jacksonville, Florida), 1959 (Box 25)
    - C Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 25)
    - Case Studies, 1957-1958 (Box 25)
    - Class Census Reports, 1960 (Box 25)
    - Class Schedule, 1961 (Box 25)
    - Clippings, 1961-1963, undated (Box 25)
    - Clippings and Photos, 1961-1963, undated (Box 25)
    - Codes, Law School Budget, 1957-1961 (Box 25)
    - College Mailing for 1962, 1960-1962 (Box 25)
    - Commencement Exercises and Data, 1959-1962, undated (Box 25)
    - Commonwealth Studies Center, 1957-1959 (Box 25)
    - Conference, Soviet Impact on International Law, 1963-1964, undated (Box 25)
    - Committees, 1959-1961 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence with Alumni, 1962-1963 (Box 25)
    - Course Schedules, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1954, 1958-1964, undated (Box 25)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1962-1965, undated (Box 25)
    - Curriculum Committee, Cavers Plan or New Plan, 1941, undated (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Curriculum Committee, Cavers Plan or New Plan Report, 1941, undated (Box 25)
    - Currie, Brainerd, 1958-1966, undated (3 folders) (Box 25)
    - Currie, Brainerd, Admiralty Rules Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 25)
    - D Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 25)
    - Davis, John Samuel, 1963-1964, undated (Box 25)
    - Dean's Report to President, 1958-1964, undated (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Dean's Special Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Deanship (McClain's Resignation and Information RE: Prospects), 1957-1958 (Box 25)
    - Delta Theta Phi Fraternity, 1962-1963 (Box 25)
    - Directory, Law Alumni, 1958-1961 (Box 25)
    - Douglas, Justice (Speech Made on Law Day, 1961), 1961 (Box 25)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1958-1966, undated (Box 25)
    - Duke International Law Society, 1961-1962 (Box 25)
    - Duke Law Journal, 1958-1966 (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Duke Law Reporter, 1960-1962, undated (Box 26)
    - Duke University Departmental Administrative Officers, 1960 (Box 26)
    - Duke University, General, 1960-1965, undated (Box 26)
    - Duke University Research Council, 1961-1962 (Box 26)
    - Duke University Traffic Commission, 1961 (Box 26)
    - Dunbar, Joe Halliday, 1964-1965, undated (Box 26)
    - E Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 26)
    - Edens, President A. Hollis, 1958-1960 (Box 26)
    - Edens-Gross Resignation, 1960 (Box 26)
    - Edens-Gross Resignation Clippings, 1960, undated (Box 26)
    - Emerson, Frank, 1959, undated (Box 26)
    - Enrollment, Duke Law School, 1960-1961 (Box 26)
    - Equipment, Air-Conditioner, etc., 1958-1963, undated (Box 26)
    - F Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 26)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1958-1966 (Box 26)
    - Faculty Committees, undated (Box 26)
    - Faculty Personnel Applications, 1957 (Box 26)
    - Faculty Publications, 1960-1962, undated (Box 26)